Guide to the Albert R. Mann papers, 1916-1931.
Mann, Albert R. papers, 1916-1931.
- Cornell University Related Materials, 1917-1931
  - Rural Social Organization, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 79)
    Sanderson, E. Dwight
  - Rural Social Organization, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 80)
  - Rural Social Organization, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 81)
  - Rural Social Organization, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 82)
  - Secretary - College, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Secretary - College, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Secretary - University, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Secretary - University, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Treasurer, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Treasurer, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - University Christian Association, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Vegetable Gardening, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Vegetable Gardening, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Veterinary, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Zoology, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Agronomy, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Agronomy, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Agronomy, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Agronomy, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Romell, L. G., 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Romell, L. G., 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 30)
    Morrison, F. B.
  - Animal Husbandry, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Architecture, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Arts and Sciences, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Botany, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Botany, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - Botany, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - Curtis, C. E., 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - Curtis, C. E., 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - Curtis, C. E., 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - Curtis, C. E., 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - Business Office, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 45)
  - Business Office, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 46)
  - Business Office, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 47)
  - Comptroller, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 48)
  - Comptroller, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 49)
  - Comptroller, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 50)
  - Comptroller, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 51)
  - Comptroller, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 52)
  - Comptroller, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 53)
  - Publications, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 54)
  - Alumni Office, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 55)
  - Steam Reports, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 56)
  - Steam Reports, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 57)
  - Cornell Countryman, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 58)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 59)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 60)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 61)
  - Agricultural (Business), 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 62)
  - Agricultural (Business), 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 63)
  - Home Economics (Business), 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 64)
  - Veterinary College, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 65)
  - Dairy Industry, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 66)
    Sharp, Paul F.
  - Dairy Industry, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 67)
  - Dairy Industry, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 68)
  - Dairy Industry, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 69)
  - Engineering, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 70)
  - Entomology, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 71)
  - Entomology, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 72)
  - Entomology, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 73)
  - Entomology, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 74)
  - Phillips, E. F., 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 75)
  - Extension, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 76)
    Butts, G. S.
    Taylor, Charles A.
  - Extension, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 77)
  - Extension, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 78)
  - Extension, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 79)
  - Ladd, C. E., 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 80)
  - Ladd, C. E., 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 81)
  - Ladd, C. E., 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 82)
  - Ladd, C. E., 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 83)
  - Ladd, C. E., 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 84)
  - Ladd, C. E., 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 85)
  - Faculty - University, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 86)
  - Farm Bureau, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 87)
  - Farm Bureau, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 88)
  - Farm Bureau, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 89)
  - Underwood, E. Victor, 1928-1929 (Box 44, Folder 90)
  - Farm Practice, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Farm Practice, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Farm Practice, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Floriculture, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Floriculture, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Floriculture, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Forestry, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Forestry, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Forestry, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Forestry, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Graduate School, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Heads of Departments and Circular Letters, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Heads of Departments and Circular Letters, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Home Economics, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Home Economics, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Home Economics, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Home Economics, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Home Economics, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Home Economics, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Home Economics, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Home Economics, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Home Economics, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Home Economics, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Home Economics, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Home Economics, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Home Economics, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Home Economics, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Home Economics, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Meek, H. B. & Randolph, L. F., 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Meek, H. B. & Randolph, L. F., 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Meek, H. B. & Randolph, L. F., 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - Meek, H. B. & Randolph, L. F., 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Meek, H. B. & Randolph, L. F., 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Law, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Information Service, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - Information Service, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - Information Service, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - Library - College, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - Library - University, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - Medical College, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - Meteorology, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - Music Department, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - Plant Breeding, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 43)
    Myers, C. H.
    Lewis, R. D.
  - Plant Breeding, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 44)
  - Plant Breeding, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 45)
  - Plant Breeding, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 46)
  - Plant Pathology, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 47)
  - Plant Pathology, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 48)
  - Plant Pathology, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 49)
  - Plant Pathology, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 50)
  - Plant Pathology, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 51)
  - Pomology, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 52)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 53)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 54)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 55)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 56)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 57)
  - Boochever, L. C., 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 58)
  - Purchasing Office, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 59)
  - President's Office, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 60)
  - President's Office, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 61)
  - President's Office, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 62)
  - President's Office, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 63)
  - President's Office, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 64)
  - President's Office, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 65)
  - President's Office, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 66)
  - President's Office, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 67)
  - Registrar, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 68)
  - Bradford, E. F., 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 69)
  - Rural Education, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 70)
  - Rural Education, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 71)
  - Rural Education, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 72)
  - Rural Engineering, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 73)
  - Rural Social Organization, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 74)
  - Rural Social Organization, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 75)
  - Rural Social Organization, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 76)
  - Rural Social Organization, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 77)
  - Secretary - College, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 78)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 79)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 80)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 81)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 82)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Secretary - University, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Treasurer, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Treasurer, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - University Christian Association, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Vegetable Gardening, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Vegetable Gardening, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Veterinary, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    Fish, Pierre A.
  - Agricultural Economics, 1929-1930 (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1929-1930 (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1929-1930 (Box 47, Folder 42)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1929-1930 (Box 47, Folder 43)
  - Agronomy, 1929-1930 (Box 47, Folder 44)
  - Agronomy, 1929-1930 (Box 47, Folder 45)
  - Agronomy, 1929-1930 (Box 47, Folder 46)
  - Agronomy, 1929-1930 (Box 47, Folder 47)
  - Romell, L. G., 1929-1930 (Box 47, Folder 48)
  - Romell, L. G., 1929-1930 (Box 47, Folder 49)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1929-1930 (Box 47, Folder 50)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1929-1930 (Box 47, Folder 51)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1929-1930 (Box 47, Folder 52)
  - Architecture, 1929-1930 (Box 47, Folder 53)
  - Arts and Sciences, 1929-1930 (Box 47, Folder 54)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1929-1930 (Box 47, Folder 55)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1929-1930 (Box 47, Folder 56)
  - Curtis, C. E., 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Curtis, C. E., 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Curtis, C. E., 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Business Office, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Business Office, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Business Office, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Botany, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    Curtis, O. F.
  - Botany, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Chemistry, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Experiment Station Committee, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Publications Committee, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Office, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Steam Reports, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Comptroller, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Comptroller, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Comptroller, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Countryman, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Agricultural Council, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Agricultural Council, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Home Economics Council, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Veterinary Council, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Dairy Industry, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Dairy Industry, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Engineering, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Entomology, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Entomology, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Entomology, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Phillips, E. F., 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Extension, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 29)
    Taylor, C. A.
  - Extension, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - Ladd, C. E., 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Ladd, C. E., 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - Ladd, C. E., 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - Ladd, C. E., 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - College Faculty, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - University Faculty, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - Farm Bureau, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 37)
  - Farm Practice, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 38)
  - Floriculture, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 39)
  - Floriculture, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 40)
  - Forestry, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 41)
  - Graduate School, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 42)
  - Heads of Departments and Circular Letters, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 43)
  - Home Economics, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 44)
  - Home Economics, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 45)
  - Home Economics, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 46)
  - Home Economics, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 47)
  - Home Economics, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 48)
  - Home Economics, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 49)
  - Home Economics, 1929-1930 (Box 48, Folder 50)
  - Howard B. Meek & Frank H. Randolph, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Information Service, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Information Service, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Law, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Library - College, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Library - University, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Meteorology, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Music Department, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Plant Breeding, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Plant Breeding, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Plant Breeding, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Plant Pathology, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Plant Pathology, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Plant Pathology, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Plant Pathology, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Pomology, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Poultry, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Poultry, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Poultry, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Poultry, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - President's Office, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - President's Office, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - President's Office, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - President's Office, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - President's Office, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Boochever, L. C., 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Purchasing, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Registrar, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Director of Admissions, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    Bradford, E. F.
  - Rural Education, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - Rural Education, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Rural Education, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - Rural Education, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - Rural Engineering, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - Rural Social Organization, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Rural Social Organization, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - Rural Social Organization, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - Rural Social Organization, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 38)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 40)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 41)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 42)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 43)
  - Secretary - College, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 44)
  - Gibson, A. W., 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 45)
  - Secretary - University, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 46)
  - Treasurer, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 47)
  - University Christian Association, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 48)
  - Veterinary College, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 49)
    Fish, P. A.
  - Vegetable Gardening, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 50)
  - Vegetable Gardening, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 51)
  - Zoology, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 52)
  - Abstracts, 1930-1931 (Box 51, Folder 41)
  - Agricultural Economics Building, 1930-1931 (Box 51, Folder 42)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1930-1931 (Box 51, Folder 43)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1930-1931 (Box 51, Folder 44)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1930-1931 (Box 51, Folder 45)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1930-1931 (Box 51, Folder 46)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1930-1931 (Box 51, Folder 47)
  - Agricultural Engineering, 1930-1931 (Box 51, Folder 48)
  - Agronomy, 1930-1931 (Box 51, Folder 49)
  - Agronomy, 1930-1931 (Box 51, Folder 50)
  - Agronomy, 1930-1931 (Box 51, Folder 51)
  - Romell, L. G., 1930-1931 (Box 51, Folder 52)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Architecture, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Arts and Sciences, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Botany, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Botany, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Botany, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Curtis, C. E., 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Curtis, C. E., 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Curtis, C. E., 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - College Buildings and Grounds Proposal, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Business Office, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Business Office, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Business Office, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Publications Committee, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Office, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Comptroller, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Comptroller, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Comptroller, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Steam Reports, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Cornell Countryman, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Agricultural Council, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Veterinary Council, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Dairy Industry, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Education Department, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 27)
    Simpson, A. D.
  - Education Department, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Education Department, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Education Department, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - Engineering, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - Entomology, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - Entomology, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - Phillips, E. F., 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - Extension, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 35)
  - Extension, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 36)
  - Extension, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 37)
  - Extension, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 38)
  - Ladd, C. E., 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 39)
  - University Faculty, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 40)
  - Farm Bureau, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 41)
  - Foster, E. S., 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 42)
  - Farm Practice, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 43)
  - Floriculture, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 44)
  - Floriculture, 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 45)
  - Forestry, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Forestry, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Graduate School, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Heads of Departments and Circular Letters, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Heads of Departments and Circular Letters, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Home Economics, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Home Economics, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Home Economics, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Home Economics, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Home Economics, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Home Economics, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Home Economics, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Home Economics Council, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Information Service, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Law, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Library - College, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Library - College, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Library - University, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Medical College, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Meek, H. B., 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Meteorology, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Music Department, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Plant Breeding, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    Fraser, A. C.
  - Plant Breeding, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Plant Breeding, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Plant Pathology, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Plant Pathology, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Plant Pathology, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Plant Pathology, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Pomology, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Poultry, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Poultry, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Poultry, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - President's Office, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - President's Office, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - President's Office, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - President's Office, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - Boochever, L. C., 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - Purchasing, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - Purchasing, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - Director of Admissions, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 41)
  - Rural Education, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 42)
    Butterworth, J. E.
  - Rural Education, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 43)
  - Rural Education, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 44)
  - Rural Social Organization, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 45)
  - Rural Social Organization, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 46)
  - Secretary - Office, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 47)
    Smith, O. W.
  - Gibson, A. W., 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 48)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Secretary - University, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Treasurer, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Treasurer, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - University Christian Association, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Vegetable Crops, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Vegetable Crops, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Veterinary College, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Zoology, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 11)
- State and Federal Related Materials, 1916-1931
  - Agriculture in its Relation to Work of Constitutional Convention, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Hooper, H. A.
    Boutelle, C. A.
  - Attorney, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Botany, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Business Office, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Committee, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Student Affairs, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Comptroller's Office, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Cornell
    Williams, E.
  - Dairy Industry, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Drawing, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Engineering Department, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Entomology, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Comstock, Anna P.
    Herrick, Glenn W.
    Comstock, J. H.
  - Extension Committee, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Extension Teaching, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Tuck, Charles H.
  - Faculty (Agriculture), 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Farm Bureau, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Burritt, M. C.
  - Farm Bureau, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Farm Crops, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Montgomery, E. G.
  - Farm Management, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Farm Practice, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Stone, John I.
  - Farm Practice, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Floriculture, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Forestry, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Graduate School, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Graduate School, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - General, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Schramm, J. R., 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Heads of Department, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Home Economics, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Home Economics, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Home Economics, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Home Economics, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Home Economics, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Home Economics, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 34)